<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Diamond Bluff Project on Diamond Bluff Project Website</title><link>https://Diamond-Bluff.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Diamond Bluff Project on Diamond Bluff Project Website</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 15:06:30 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Diamond-Bluff.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Videos and Slides From OPI Event</title><link>https://Diamond-Bluff.github.io/posts/2022-03-18-opi-event/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 15:06:30 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://Diamond-Bluff.github.io/posts/2022-03-18-opi-event/</guid><description>The Open Programmable Infrastructure Alpha Event was a great success thanks to all of our presentors. We had great participation. See below for all of the videos and slides.
Day One OPI Event Keynote: Nick McKeown OPI Event Keynote
OPI Event Keynote: AI Training Clusters: Challenges @ DC Scale - Meta - Nic Viljoen OPIEvent - D/IPU Open API, The need for a Common Interface Framework - Dell Mark Sanders D/IPU Open API, The need for a Common Interface Framework Slides</description></item><item><title>Open Programmable Infrastructure Project Event</title><link>https://Diamond-Bluff.github.io/posts/2022-02-22-opi-event/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 14:45:30 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://Diamond-Bluff.github.io/posts/2022-02-22-opi-event/</guid><description>We are pleased to announce the Alpha edition of the Open Programmable Infrastructure (OPI) event that will be held virtually on March 15th and March 16th, 2022 from 8am-1:30pm Pacific Time. This is an exciting opportunity to share in the various community efforts underway to make infrastructure fully programmable across software and hardware devices such as IPUs, DPUs, or switches.
You can add the events to your calendar here.
The event schedule and speaker list is provided below.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://Diamond-Bluff.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Diamond-Bluff.github.io/about/</guid><description>The objective of the Diamond Bluff initiative is to foster a community-driven standards-based open ecosystem for next generation architectures and frameworks based on DPU/IPU-like technologies.</description></item><item><title>Connect</title><link>https://Diamond-Bluff.github.io/join/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Diamond-Bluff.github.io/join/</guid><description>The Open Programmable Infrastructure Project is in the early stages of forming. The Project will be the merging of the Diamond Bluff project and the IPDK Project.
The Information below is how you can participate.
Overview Slides #the-canvas { border: 1px solid black; direction: ltr; width: 100%; height: auto; display: none; } #paginator { display: none; text-align: center; margin-bottom: 10px; } #loadingWrapper { display: none; justify-content: center; align-items: center; width: 100%; height: 350px; } #loading { display: inline-block; width: 50px; height: 50px; border: 3px solid #d2d0d0;; border-radius: 50%; border-top-color: #383838; animation: spin 1s ease-in-out infinite; -webkit-animation: spin 1s ease-in-out infinite; } @keyframes spin { to { -webkit-transform: rotate(360deg); } } @-webkit-keyframes spin { to { -webkit-transform: rotate(360deg); } } Previous Next &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Page: / window.</description></item></channel></rss>